[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So now we have some training data and some desk data.
现在我们有了训练集和测试集
And what we can do next is #Build,
我们接下来做的是 #Build
there's a sub-header here,
我们在这里添加一个子标题
#Build the regression model.
建立回归模型
So GraphLab Create has many algorithms pre-implemented for
GraphLab Create有许多已经编写的算法
various machinery and tasks or you can implement your own if you like.
供不同的机器和任务使用 你也可以自己编写
And during the sequence of the specialization,
在我们专项课程期间
you're gonna write many algorithms of your own, but for this course,
你会自己写许多算法 但这次课
we're just gonna use pre-implemented algorithms so
我们只是用内置的算法
can really try to understand how machine learning works.
这样的话你就能真正试着去理解 机器学习是怎么进行的
So what you can do with machine learning?
所以你怎么来实现机器学习呢？
So, we're gonna do is a build a square foot prediction model.
我们准备建立一个平方英尺的预测模型
Just call it sqft_model.
把它命名为sqft_model
And in GraphLab, there something called linear regression.
在GraphLab中 有个称为线性回归的函数
So, linear regression is what we learned, what we explored and
线性回归是我们已经学习、探索
talked about, and we understood quite well during the module that Ann was teaching.
并且讨论过的东西 我们在Ann讲授的模块中对它有了充分的了解
And so if you just say linear _regression.create,
既然这样 如果你只敲下 linear_regression.create
it's going to create a linear regression model for you.
它就会为你创建一个线性回归模型
That creates the traits with projects GraphLab Create, and
然后它使用GraphLab Create项目建立了图形
create is also the verb to use to create various things with GraphLab Create.
create同样也是用GraphLab Create来 创造各种各样形状的关键词
So we're now going to create a linear regression model, and
我们现在准备建立创建一个线性回归模型
what I have to give as input I give it the training data.
我需要给它一个输入 我将训练集作为输入
So here's the training data.
这是我们的训练集
You have to say what variable you're trying to predict.
你还需要说明你想预测哪个变量
So that's the target.
这称为目标
So I'm gonna say the target is going to be price.
我准备将目标设为价格
So I'm trying to predict price.
这就是说 我要预测价格
And the question is what are the features, what is the input.
那么问题是 输入与特征有什么不同
So, I'm going to say that the features, and by the way, you can use top complete
我想说明的是 顺便提一下 即使你在
even if [INAUDIBLE] parameters of function, which is pretty cool.
敲函数的参数时也是可以使用便捷的自动补全功能
So, the features is a list of the features.
话说回来 特征是一系列特征
If you don't give anything, it will use all features, all columns of the data.
如果你不给函数输入的话 它会使用所有的特征 全部的数据
But here, the only feature input we want to use is square feet of living space.
但现在 我们想使用的输入特征只是 居住面积
And that is a string that I need to put in, so
我需要在里面放个字符串
I forgot to put it in quotes, so let me fix that real quick here.
我忘记把它放在引号里了 让我来快速改正一下
So open quotes,
前引号
close quotes.
后引号
All right, very good.
好了
So let me just reread that for us.
让我们再快速浏览一下
So sqft_model graphlab.linear_regression.create on
soft_model = graphlab.linear_regression.create
the training data to predict the target price using features sqft of living.
用了训练集中的数据 预测目标是价格 使用居住面积作为特征
Let's go an execute this.
让我们来执行一下
On training data training, I wrote data twice here.
在训练集这里出问题了 我写了两次data
You see the arrow came out here, training data and the score data.
你可以看到错误发生在这里 训练集
So now let's execute.
现在让我们执行一下
So what's happening here?
现在发生了什么？
It's done actually, but what we did was create a linear regression model,
它实际上执行了 我们做的是创建一个线性回归模型
it used a particular algorithm called Newton's Method.
它使用了一种特定的算法——牛顿迭代法
But GraphLab Create chooses an algorithm automatically for
GraphLab Create会自动为你选择算法
you unless you tell it which one to use.
除非你告诉它使用哪一个
And this algorithm allows you to make some predictions on the data.
这个算法允许你对数据做一些预测
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community